好的
Okay.
嘿 老爸 这个周末我能和艾薇一家出去玩吗
Hey, dad, can I go away with Ivy and her family this weekend?
艾薇说她家在湖边有幢小别墅
Ivy says they have a nice house on the Lake.
玩一个周末
A weekend getaway?
湖边小屋 还点上篝火
House on the Lake? Crackling fire?
你问下能不能带朋友去
Can you bring a friend?
或者 带老爸去吧
Or a dad?
怎么说呢 有你在的话 玩起来就
Kind of... it's not a getaway unless I get away from...
我吗
Me?
谢谢你能理解我
Thanks for understanding.
-去吧 -谢谢 爱你哦
- Have fun. - Love you!
我们回来了 老爸
Hey, dad.
-嗨老爸 -最近怎么样
- Hey, dad. - How are you doing?
你们有什么需要坦白的吗
Anything you boys care to tell me?
你怎么会觉得我们需要坦白什么
What makes you think we want to tell you something?
自己看吧
That.
您又来拜访了啊 达布尼太太
Well well well, Mrs. Dabney.
还带了个棒球和卫星天线
With a baseball and a satellite dish.
-要怎么赔偿呢 -不用你担心
- What do I owe you? - Don't worry about it.
我还记着你的信用卡号呢
I still have your credit card number on file.
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录 www.Deefun.com
生活搞得一团糟
<i>Today's all burnt toast </i>
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
<i>Running late, and dad jokes</i>
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
<i>Has anybody seen my left shoe</i>
■
翻译： Ragner24 Johnny-Z
我闭上眼  咬口早餐
<i>I close my eyes, take a bite</i>
跳上车子  放声大笑
<i>Grab a ride, laugh out loud</i>
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
<i>There it is up on the roof</i>
■
校订： line
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
<i>I've been there, I've survived</i>
所以听取我的建议
<i>So just take my advice</i>
■
后期： Johnny-Z liloelva
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
世界有很多疯狂无奈
<i>Things are crazy</i>
可是我知道你会有美好将来
<i>But I know your future's bright</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
不要怀疑
<i>There's no maybe</i>
一切终会如你所愿
<i>Everything turns out all right</i>
生活有悲有喜
<i>Your life is up and down</i>
但是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
<i>But trust me it comes back around</i>
你会喜欢将来的你
<i>You're gonna love</i> <i>who you turn out to be</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby.</i>
查莉成长日记  第二季第三十集（本季完）
Good Luck Charlie  S02E30  Teddy on Ice
嘿 查莉宝贝儿
Hey, Charlie.
-你怎么坐在这里 -被妈妈罚的
- Whatcha doing? - Timeout.
-怎么会 -我做坏事了
- What happened? - I was bad.
老公过来 有事和你商量
Could I talk to you in here for a minute?
这个椅子是用来罚坐的
That's a timeout chair?
我一直以为是盖比专座呢
This whole time I thought it was just Gabe's chair.
到底怎么回事
What's going on?
老公 这事情都快把我烦死了
Bob, I am so upset.
查莉今天在幼儿园里说脏字了
Charlie said a bad word at school today.
什么 她说什么了
What? What did she say?
额
Whoa.
我们的宝贝女儿居然说这个
Our little girl said that?
当时她在用通心粉做项链
Well, apparently she was making.
然后有个小朋友推了她一下
A macaroni necklace when some kid pushed her,
通心粉掉地上了 查莉就说了这个词
Knocked her macaroni and out came the word.
这样啊 至少她用对地方了
Well, at least she used it correctly.
其实老师说她骂得相当没水平
Actually her teacher said she's swearing at a second-grade level.
我还是无法想象我们的小天使会说这样的话
I just can't picture our little angel saying something like that.
我也这么觉得
Me neither.
不行 告诉你吧
No, I'm sorry. You know what?
除非我自己听到 不然我绝不相信
Until I hear that myself, I don't believe it.
没错
You're right.
看看查莉 她集合了我们孩子的所有优点
I mean Charlie is the perfect combination of all of our kids.
像泰迪一样聪明
She's got the intelligence of Teddy,
像PJ一样可爱
The sweetness of P.J.
而且完全不像盖比
And none of Gabe.
我们的征途在大山深处 向着群山我们迈开步伐
To the mountains we will go, the mountains we will go
向着可爱的山中小屋
To our cabin in the mountains
全家和泰迪一起前进
The Wentzes and Teddy will go.
这个小调怎么样 泰迪
How was that one, Teddy?
呃 目前为止最最好听的
Oh, best one yet.
他们就要这样一路唱过去吗
Are they gonna do this the whole way?
如果你刚问会不会一路唱过去
If you just said, "do they do this the whole way?"
那我告诉你 会的
The answer is yes.
对了 泰迪 你觉得我们这辆新车怎么样
So, Teddy, what do you think about the new car?
噢 还不错哦
- Oh, it's... it's nice.
在你把我们的旧车小格蕾西撞坏之后
Bought this one right after you wrecked.
我在二十分钟内就决定买了这辆新的
My old car Gracie in less than 20 minutes.
-还记得么 -终身难忘啊
- Remember that? - Sure do.
那天我看到你开着我们的小车的时候 就有不祥的预感了
I had such a bad feeling when I saw you drive her away that day,
但我没有阻止你
But I didn't say anything.
真是后悔死了
I'll never forgive myself for that.
我们的征途在大山深处
To the mountains we will go
向着群山我们迈开步伐
The mountains we will go
向着....
To the...
现在呢 查莉
Okay, Charlie,
爸爸妈妈要教你关于词语的事情
Mommy and daddy want to talk to you today about words,
-特别是新的词 -好呀
- Especially new words. - Okay.
我们假设呢 有人
So let's say somebody.
把你的果汁打翻了
Knocked over your juice.
那你会说什么呢
Now what would you say to that?
糟了
Oopsy.
如果你真的对此很不开心呢
But if you really didn't like it?
啊哦
Uh-oh.
好吧好吧 那么这样
Okay okay, let's...
如果有人抢走了你的果汁
Let's say somebody took your juice.
像这样 你会怎么说
Huh? What would you say then?
或者有人抢走了你的果汁
Or if somebody took your juice.
还喷得你到处都湿透了
And then did this all over you?
你是想引她说那个词还是想逼我说
Are we trying to get her to say the word or me to say the word?
-老公 我们这样太傻了 -的确
-Bob, this is silly. -I know!
她现在不会说 因为她根本就从来没说过
She's not saying it now because she never said it in the first place.
没错 她从来就没说过
Exactly, she never said it.
来吧 宝贝儿
Come on, sweetie.
我们去帮爸爸拿件干净的衬衫
Let's go get daddy a new shirt.
-她刚说俄 -什么 她居然说了
- She said it. - She said it?
她把娃娃掉到地上 然后就说了
She dropped her doll and she said it.
不是吧 查莉 你不会吧
Oh, Charlie, you didn't.
我真的说了 爸爸
I did, daddy.
您为什么不进来呢
Won't you come in?
喂 那个节目我们正在看呢
Hey hey, we were watching that.
抱歉 我要看的电视剧开始了
Too bad. My story is on.
谁让你弄坏了我的卫星天线 我只能到这儿来看了
And since you broke my dish, I'll be watching my show here.
想吃爆米花 记得先打个招呼
If you want some of my popcorn, ask for it.
-我能吃你的爆米花吗 -没你的份儿
- Can I have some of your popcorn? - No.
你要看什么节目俄
So what is this show?
《明日之泪》
It's called "The Tears of Tomorrow."
讲述缅因州未来城的泪珠一家
It's about the tears family of tomorrow, Maine.
上一集里 蔡斯·泪珠发现
In the last episode, Chance Tears found out.
他的第七任妻子阿曼达其实是克隆的
His seventh wife Amanda is actually a Clone.
保持安静 开始了
Quiet. It's starting.
今天的伤痛带来《明日之泪》
From the heartaches of today come "The Tears of Tomorrow."
好吧 我们可以闪了 老哥
Yeah, let's go, P.J.
-喔 慢着 这是谁啊 -是蒂芙尼·泪珠
- Whoa, uh, who... who's that? - That's Tiffany Tears.
她出现的时候永远只穿着一件小号比基尼
All she ever wears is a tiny bikini.
太恶心了
It's disgusting.
是啊
Sure is.
噢 这个是布里克·泪珠
Ooh, and that's Brick Tears.
他是蔡斯的外孙 才十二岁
He's chance's 12-year-old grandson.
他真是个邪恶的小天才
He's a boy genius with a taste for evil.
坐过去一点
Move over!
阿曼达 这位是谁
Amanda, who is this?
蔡斯 我很荣幸向你介绍
I'm glad you asked, chance.
这是我新交的男朋友 昌西
This is my new boyfriend Chauncey.
你说什么 他看上去长得和我一模一样
What? But he looks just like me.
没错 你不是唯一一个会克隆技术的人
That's right. You're not the only one who knows how to Clone.
哈 出乎意料啊 编剧太有才了
Man, I did not see that coming.
快看布里克 他手里拿着什么
Oh, there's Brick. What's he got in his hand?
布里克 你手里拿着什么
Brick, what do you have in your hand?
-布里克 快放下武器 -不
Brick, put that weapon down! No!
噢
Oh!
欲知后事如何 请听下回分解
These have been... "The Tears of Tomorrow."
什么 就这样结束了
Wait. That's it?
-布里克怎么样了 -蒂芙尼怎么样了
- But what about brick? - And what about Tiffany?
她去换泳装了怎么还没回来
She went to change bathing suits and never came back.
别着急呀 节目明天继续
Calm down. The show's on again tomorrow.
明天还有
Tomorrow?
没想到还有这出
I did not see that coming!
好了 同志们 我们安全抵达
All right, everybody, we're here.
房子在哪里
Where's the house?
这个嘛 泰迪你看 就在那里呢
Oh, Teddy, it's right out there.
就那个湖上的小棚屋
That shack on the Lake?
艾薇 你说的可是一幢漂亮的小楼啊
Ivy, you said it was a nice house.
不对 我说的就漂着的小屋
No, I said it was an ice house.
但是我承认我说话的确发音不准
But I'll admit, I do run my words together.
-好 终于到了 -到了耶
- Oh yes, we made it! - Well, here we are.
来呀 泰迪 我带你看看这里
Oh, Teddy, let me give you the tour.
-有什么要问的吗 -呃 就一个
- Any questions? - Uh, just one.
你们就用这个来方便吗
Is that the bathroom?
噢 当然不是了 这是用来钓鱼的
Oh no. That's our fishing hole.
钓鱼当晚餐
That's where we catch our dinner.
艾薇 我能占用你一小会儿吗
Ivy, could I talk to you for a sec?
我给你们一点私人空间
Let me give you girls some privacy.
你又耍我
You tricked me!
我实话实说的话你就不会来了
I knew you wouldn't come if I told you the truth.
被你说对了 我真的不会来的
Yeah, you're right, I totally wouldn't have come!
喂 别抱怨了 没你想象的那么糟
Ugh, stop complaining. It's not so bad.
不遭么 地板上都有一个洞呢
There is a hole in the floor.
还好吗
Everything okay in here?
噢 还好 还好
Oh yes, it is.
拉个破帘子还能听到我们 那还有什么用
What is the point of a curtain if she can hear us?
不知道 你怎么还悄声细语的
I don't know. And why are you still whispering?
你们的问题都很好
Those are two good questions.
好了 你们找我什么事
So, uh, what did you guys wanna talk to me about?
我们问你几个问题
We'll ask the questions around here.
你为什么要教查莉脏字
Now why did you teach Charlie that bad word?
-什么脏字 -别跟我装傻
- What bad word? - Don't play dumb with me!
明白吗 别敬酒不吃吃罚酒
All right? We can do this the easy way or the hard way.
-你选吧 兔崽子 -喔 喔 喔 喔
- Your choice, punk! - Whoa whoa whoa whoa! Whoa whoa!
亲爱的 亲爱的 你先去消消气
Sweetie, sweetie, why don't you go take a break?
消消气
Go take a break.
让我和他谈
Lme talk to the boy.
哇 你老妈暴走了
Wow, your old mom's pretty riled up, huh?
知道吗 盖比 有时候我们会犯错误
You know, Gabe, sometimes we make mistakes.
但更关键的是 我们要勇于承认错误
But the important thing is to tell the truth.
和你老爸摊牌吧
You can tell your old dad the truth, right?
爸 歇歇吧 我知道你们的把戏了
Dad, you can stop. I know what you're doing.
-什么把戏 -跟我唱红脸白脸
- What do you mean? - You're playing good cop/bad cop.
什么 亲爱的 他看穿了
What... honey, he's onto us!
-噢 天啊 -你们一开始就想错了
- Oh, man! - Yeah, and there's a little problem with your theory.
如果我要教查莉脏字
For me to teach Charlie a bad word,
我就要和那个小丫头耗上半天
I'd actually have to spend time with her.
你可以走了
You're free to go.
-查莉说脏话了 -嗯嗯
- Charlie said a bad word? - Mm-hmm.
-什么脏话 -你心里清楚
- What was it? - We think you know.
我不清楚
No, I don't.
太不入耳了
That's terrible.
这词是什么意思
What does it mean?
你可以走了
You're free to go.
鉴于查莉经常在后院里玩
And since Charlie spends a lot of time in our backyard,
我们认为她有可能从你那里
We think she might have heard something.
耳濡目染到一些东西
From your side of the fence.
关我屁事
What are you accusing me of?
查莉说脏字了 我们认为
Charlie said a bad word and we think.
她有可能是从你那里学到的
She might have learned it from you.
什么脏字
What was the word?
我又不是对你说的
I wasn't saying it to you!
让你不敢再说第二遍
You sure won't be saying it twice.
泰迪 介绍你认识下老贝琪
Teddy, I'd like for you to meet old Betsy.
她还有一段小故事呢
There's a little story that goes along with her.
噢 老爹 等一等
Oh, hold on a second, dad.
说吧
Go ahead.
贝琪是我祖父送给我的礼物
Betsy was a present from my grandfather.
没错 他用房后的一棵树 雕刻出了她的手柄
Yeah. He carved her handle from a tree behind his house.
就在我十岁那年 拥有了她
I've had her since I was 10 years old.
好了 让她下水吧
All right, let's get her in the water.
哈里 让泰迪来吧
Harry, let Teddy do it.
我认为有些不妥吧 玛丽露
I don't think that's a good idea, Mary Lou,
特别是除了格雷西那档子事儿之后
Especially after what happened to Gracie...
我已经把它忘干净了
Which I've forgotten about.
哈里 泰迪是客人 咱们要做出地主之谊
Harry, Teddy is our guest. Now make a gesture.
我不想尽地主之谊
I don't wanna make a gesture!
他没必要尽地主之谊
He doesn't have to make a gesture.
哈里 大度点儿
Harry, gesture!
拿好了
Here.
好了 甩杆
All right, cast away.
不错 对于新手来说
Not bad for a rookie.
谢谢夸奖 自从我很小的时候
Thanks, I've been holding stuff.
就会握东西了
Since I was little.
现在激动人心的时刻到了
And now the excitement begins.
激动人心的时刻是马上到了还是
Is the excitement still beginning or...
已经到了
Are we... are we in it now?
哈里 能帮我个忙吗
Harry, can you give me a hand?
噢 好的 好的 没问题
Oh yes yes. Good good.
-自己玩吧 我去厕所了 -厕所在哪
- Have fun. I'm off to the restroom. - Where is it?
就是个肮脏恶臭的坑
It's a nasty outhouse.
在冰面上比比皆是
All the way across the freezing Lake.
在那里没有我爹娘 所以再脏再臭也无妨
But it's away from my parents, so I enjoy it.
噢
Oh!
贝琪 不要啊
Betsy! Noooo!
不会吧
Oh no!
他们取消了《明日之泪》的演出
They canceled "Tears of Tomorrow."
什么
What?!
但是这部剧好像已经播出五十年了 为什么会停播呢
But it's been on for, like, 50 years. Why now?
他们说这部剧不适合咱们这一代人看
It says our generation doesn't respond to it.
胡扯
That's crazy.
知道吗 也许孩子们放下了
You know, maybe if the kids.
手中的手机 电子游戏还有玩具
Put down all the phones and the video games and the gadgets.
转而去死心塌地去追这部剧
And actually watched the darn program...
我们是不是和达布尼夫人呆的时间有些长了
Do you think we're spending too much time with Mrs. Dabney?
那还用说
Hogwash.
-又是她 -我们要和她谈谈了
- That's her. - I guess we have to tell her.
好啊 孩子们
Hello, boys.
达布尼夫人 请进
Mrs. Dabney, come on in.
请坐
Have a seat.
告诉你个坏消息
We have some bad news.
-你是说坏消息吗 -是的
- Bad news, you say? - Yes.
-什么 -什么什么
- What is it? - What's what?
坏消息是什么
What's the bad news?
你最好坐下
You'd better sit down.
坐着呢
I am sitting.
好了 没什么可说的 除了
Well, there's nothing left to say but...
结束了
It's over.
什么结束了
What's over?
他们停播了
They canceled
《明日之泪》
"The Tears of Tomorrow."
什么 不
What?! No!
我 噢
I... oh!
-她是晕过去了吗 -还是
- Did she faint? - Or is she...
我们晚餐只有米饭吗
So all we're having for dinner is rice?
这个嘛 通常会有一条鱼在上面的
Well, usually there's fish on top of it.
但是某人把鱼竿弄消失了
But someone lost our means of catching fish.
鱼竿就是老贝琪
And by that, I mean old Betsy.
某人 也就是你
And by someone, I mean you.
温兹先生 我保证 我一回到家
Mr. Wentz, I promise, right when we get home
我马上再给您买一支鱼竿
I'll get you another fishing pole.
你能唤醒我的祖父 让他为其雕刻吗
And are you gonna raise my grandfather from the dead to carve it?
哈里 能和你谈谈吗 私下里
Harry, can I talk to you for a minute in private?
你要改变一下你的态度
You have got to change your attitude.
泰迪可是我们的客人
Teddy is our guest!
玛丽露 那姑娘就是个杀手
Mary Lou, the girl is an assassin.
首先她杀死了格雷西 如今她又淹死了贝琪
First she killed Gracie, and now she's drowned Betsy!
幸好是私下里谈话
Sure glad that's a private conversation.
还好吧 达布尼夫人
You okay, Mrs. Dabney?
我好不了了
I'll never be okay again.
没了蔡斯·泪珠我可怎么活啊
I don't know how I can go on without Chance Tears.
别这么说 至少你和蔡斯已经相伴多年
Well, at least you and chance had a lot of years together.
我和蒂芙尼才刚刚认识
Tiffany and I just met.
好了 别难过了
All right, come on.
咱们找找能带走这片阴霾的节目
Let's try to find something to take our minds off our loss.
别开玩笑了 我对这部剧坚贞不渝
Are you kidding? I've been watching that show forever.
你觉得我会用这种烂剧来填补心灵的空白吗
You think I'm gonna replace it just like that?
嘿 这是什么
Hey, what's this?
尽管时光荏苒 但是你绝不会离弃
Though time may pass, you will never be far
《昨日之巅》
From "The Edge of Yesterday."
呜 看着不错
Ooh, that looks good.
不敢相信我们抓不到
I can't believe we never found out.
教给查莉脏字的那个人
Who taught Charlie that word.
我困惑了 老鲍
I don't know, Bob.
也许她从哪学到的脏字并不重要
Maybe it's not important where she learned it.
重要的是我们应该教会她
What's important is that we teach Charlie.
骂人是不对的
That cursing is wrong.
我觉着我们做的不错
And I think we've done that.
怎么不打转向灯啊 你个
How about a turn signal, you...
结案了
Case closed.
艾薇
Ivy.
-艾薇 艾薇 -干嘛
- Ivy, Ivy. - What?
我要去厕所
I have to go to the bathroom.
-在哪啊 -就是个坑
- Where is it? - It's an outhouse.
我出门 闻着臭味就找到了
You go outside and you follow the stench.
谢了
Thank you.
哇
Whoa!
-什么声音 -泰迪落水了
What was that? Teddy fell in the Lake!
-额滴神啊 快点 -噢 泰迪
- Oh my goodness, come on! - Oh, Teddy!
拉 大家使劲拉
Pull! Everybody pull hard!
加油 好了
Come on! All right.
噢 什么东西 搞什么
Oh, what's that? What's going on?
-啊 -哇 嘿 你抓了条鱼
- Aah! - Wow. Hey, you caught a fish.
哇 好漂亮的一条鱼
Whoa, and it's a beauty.
看 看 有条线在它的嘴里
Look. Look, there's a line in its mouth.
什么
What?
噢 噢 是贝琪
Oh. Oh, Betsy!
噢 可把我想死了 宝贝
Oh, I missed you so much, baby.
泰迪 亲爱的 没事吧
Teddy, honey, are you okay?
没事 没事 我就是 我没事 就是有点冷
Yeah, no, I'm just... I'm fine. I'm just kind of cold.
-好了 -好了 泰迪
- Okay. - Well, Teddy,
看来你已经完成自我救赎了
Looks like you've redeemed yourself.
我们邀请你明年还与我们共度美好时光
You are officially invited back next year.
不
Noooo!
好了 查莉 今天给你好好上一课
Well, Charlie, a big life lesson today...
听着 当某人说他有个环湖别墅
See, when someone says they have a house on the Lake,
意思可能就是他们有个房子建在了湖上
They might mean they have a house on the Lake.
这节课感觉怪怪的 但是
Kind of an offbeat lesson, but...
其实 根本不算是节课
Well, not really a lesson at all.
先不管了 以后再修改视频
Give me a break. I've gotta do a lot of these.
好了 至少家里的某人
Well, at least one person in the family.
好好上了一课
Learned something.
能放了我吗 好无聊啊
Can I go now? This is boring.
-不 -是吗
- No! - Yeah?
好吧 如果你认为我会老老实实地坐在这把椅子上
Well, if you think I'm gonna sit in this chair.
整整二十分钟 噢 噢 好运吧 查莉
The entire 20 minutes, ho ho, good luck, Charlie.
比我说得好
Couldn't have said it better myself.
今天的伤痛
From the heartaches of today
带来《明日之泪》
Come "The Tears of Tomorrow."
你吓不住我
You can't threaten me.
我是蔡斯·泪珠
I'm Chance Tears.
好啊 蔡斯
Hello, Chance.
阿曼达
Amanda!
你来干什么
What are you doing here?
我也想知道
That's what I'd like to know.
克隆人阿曼达 但是
Amanda Clone! But...
我来处理 蔡斯
I'll handle it, Chance.
克隆人蔡斯
Chance Clone!
布里克
Brick!
这里发生了什么
What's goin' on here?
我就知道这天会到来的
I knew this day would come.
-我也是 -我也是
- Me too. - Me too.
我也是
Me too
我晕了
I'm confuse.
谁才是真身
Who's the real one?
管他呢
Who cares?
你两个 我两个
You take two. I take two.
以上就是本集《明日之泪》的精彩内容
These have been..."The Tears of Tomorrow."